var questions=[
{
	question:"Where and when was the first case of Corona virus identified?",
	options:{
		a:'Wuhan, China on January 2020',
		b:'Tokyo,Japan on October 2019',
		c:'Wuhan, China on December 2019',
		d:"New Delhi, India on April 2020 "
	},
	answer:'c'
},
{
	question:"Which country has the most number of confirmed COVID-19 cases as of August 2020",
	options:{
		a:'China',
		b:'India',
		c:'USA',
		d:"Germany"
	},
	answer:'c'
},
{
	question:"Which of the following is not a common symptom among people who had COVID-19?",
	options:{
		a:'Fever',
		b:'Weight loss',
		c:'Fatigue',
		d:"Cough"
	},
	answer:'b'
},
{
	question:"Which state of India has the most number of confirmed COVID-19 cases as of August 2020",
	options:{
		a:'Tamil Nadu',
		b:'China',
		c:'Kerala',
		d:"Maharashtra"
	},
	answer:'d'
},
{
	question:"Which of the following age group of people are at the highest risk of getting severe COVID-19 infection?",
	options:{
		a:'60+',
		b:'15 to 20',
		c:'20 to 25',
		d:"25 to 33"
	},
	answer:'a'
},
{
	question:"Coronaviruses are common human and animal viruses.How many different viruses of the Coronavirus family are know to cause disease among humans?",
	options:{
		a:'6',
		b:'7',
		c:'3',
		d:"2"
	},
	answer:'b'
},
{
	question:"Which organ in the body does the Coronavirus primarily attack?",
	options:{
		a:'Heart',
		b:'Interstine',
		c:'Kidney',
		d:"Lungs"
	},
	answer:'d'
},
{
	question:"Which of the following institutions started the first vaccine trial for COVID-19?",
	options:{
		a:'Oxford University',
		b:'Harvard University',
		c:'MIT',
		d:"None of the above"
	},
	answer:'a'
},
{
	question:"How many people have been infected by Coronavirus as of August 2020?",
	options:{
		a:'10 million',
		b:'15 million',
		c:'22.9 million',
		d:"87.765 million"
	},
	answer:'c'
},
{
	question:"The Coronavirus that caused a global pandemic this year is also known as",
	options:{
		a:'SARS-CoV-2 ',
		b:'COVID-19',
		c:'Both A and B',
		d:"None of the above"
	},
	answer:'c'
}
]
// var questions=[
// {
// 	question:"Where and when was the first case of Corona virus identified?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'Wuhan, China on January 2020',
// 		b:'Tokyo,Japan on October 2019',
// 		c:'Wuhan, China on December 2020',
// 		d:"New Delhi, India on April 2020 "
// 	},
// 	answer:'c'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Which country has the most number of confirmed COVID-19 cases as of August 2020",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'China',
// 		b:'India',
// 		c:'USA',
// 		d:"Germany"
// 	},
// 	answer:'c'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Which of the following is not a common symptom among people who had COVID-19?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'Fever',
// 		b:'Weight loss',
// 		c:'Fatigue',
// 		d:"Cough"
// 	},
// 	answer:'b'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Which state of India has the most number of confirmed COVID-19 cases as of August 2020",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'Tamil Nadu',
// 		b:'China',
// 		c:'Kerala',
// 		d:"Maharashtra"
// 	},
// 	answer:'d'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Which of the following age group of people are at the highest risk of getting severe COVID-19 infection?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'60+',
// 		b:'15 to 20',
// 		c:'20 to 25',
// 		d:"25 to 33"
// 	},
// 	answer:'a'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Coronaviruses are common human and animal viruses.How many different viruses of the Coronavirus family are know to cause disease among humans?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'6',
// 		b:'7',
// 		c:'3',
// 		d:"2"
// 	},
// 	answer:'b'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Which organ in the body does the Coronavirus primarily attack?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'Heart',
// 		b:'Interstine',
// 		c:'Kidney',
// 		d:"Lungs"
// 	},
// 	answer:'d'
// },
// {
// 	question:"Which of the following institutions started the first vaccine trial for COVID-19?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'Oxford University',
// 		b:'Harvard University',
// 		c:'MIT',
// 		d:"None of the above"
// 	},
// 	answer:'a'
// },
// {
// 	question:"How many people have been infected by Coronavirus as of August 2020?",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'10 million',
// 		b:'15 million',
// 		c:'22.9 million',
// 		d:"87.765 million"
// 	},
// 	answer:'c'
// },
// {
// 	question:"The Coronavirus that caused a global pandemic this year is also known as",
// 	options:{
// 		a:'SARS-CoV-2 ',
// 		b:'COVID-19',
// 		c:'Both A and B',
// 		d:"None of the above"
// 	},
// 	answer:'c'
// }
// ]